If
If you
If you think
If you think you're
If you think you're fast
If you think you're fast, well...
I'm
I'm a
I'm a li
I'm a little
I'm a little fas
I'm a little faster
You're
You're like
You're like a
You're like a ga
You're like a gazelle
I'm
I'm a
I'm a li
I'm a lion
I'm a lion 'bout
I'm a lion 'bout to
I'm a lion 'bout to catch
I'm a lion 'bout to catch ya
I'm
I'm in
I'm in the
I'm in the mood
I'm in the mood for
I'm in the mood for a
Diss
Disstrack
Disstrack ven
Disstrack venture
You're
You're so
You're so weak
I'm
I'mma
I'mma put
I'mma put you
I'mma put you on
I'mma put you on a
I'mma put you on a stretch
I'mma put you on a stretcher
Blo
Blocking
Blocking you
Blocking you out
Blocking you out like
La
La-la
La-la-lah
Might
Might as
Might as well
Might as well be
Might as well be do
Might as well be doing
Might as well be doing this
So
Solo
Solo-lah
Put
Put a
Put a hole
Put a hole in
Put a hole in you
Put a hole in you like
Brah
Brah-brah
Brah-brah-brah
I
I just
I just can't
I just can't con
I just can't control
I just can't control that
Hah
Hah-hah
Hah-hah-hah
Li
Little
Little ba
Little baby
Little baby boy
Play
Play you
Play you like
Play you like a
Play you like a toy
I'll
I'll o
I'll obli
I'll oblite
I'll obliterate
I'll obliterate you
I'm
I'mma
I'mma take
I'mma take out
I'mma take out all
I'mma take out all your
I'mma take out all your joy
With
With me
Bet
Bet, I'm
Bet, I'mma
Bet, I'mma take
Bet, I'mma take it
Bet, I'mma take it with
Bet, I'mma take it with me
With
With me
Bet
Bet, I'm
Bet, I'mma
Bet, I'mma take
Bet, I'mma take it
Bet, I'mma take it with
Bet, I'mma take it with me
Blo
Blocking
Blocking you
Blocking you out
Blocking you out like
La
La-la
La-la-lah
Might
Might as
Might as well
Might as well be
Might as well be do
Might as well be doing
Might as well be doing this
So
Solo
Solo-lah
Put
Put a
Put a hole
Put a hole in
Put a hole in you
Put a hole in you like
Brah
Brah-brah
Brah-brah-brah
I
I just
I just can't
I just can't con
I just can't control
I just can't control that
Hah
Hah-hah
Hah-hah-hah
Keep
Keep it
Keep it down
Watch
Watch what
Watch what your
Watch what your mouth
Watch what your mouth say
Shut
Shut your
Shut your mouth
Shut
Shut your
Shut your mouth
Shut your mouth, no
Shut your mouth, no, no
Li
Little
Little boy
Little boy you
Little boy you won
Little boy you won I'm
Little boy you won I'm a
Little boy you won I'm a lo
Little boy you won I'm a loser
Knock
Knock me
Knock me down
Knock
Knock me
Knock me down
Knock me down, no
Knock me down, no no
Knock me down, no no-oh
I
I tried
I tried my
I tried my best